JOE WILES: We're counting down our top 80 most downloaded internet guitar tabs and coming in at number 22 is "Thunderstruck" by AC/DC.
Let's take a look.
Now this is a really good hammer-on pull off exercise, okay?
It's all going to occur on the B string--okay?
What we're going to do is we're going to hammer-on with our index finger to the 4th fret.
We're going to pull it off--and up to the 8th fret--I'm sorry, the 7th fret.
So, 4 to 7.
Hammer-on, pull off, 7th fret, pull off, 4th, open, 7th, open.
I'll tell you that slowly with me.
4, open, 7, open, 4, open, 7, open, 4, open, 7, open, 4, open, 7, open.
Now, we're going to move this two fingers up so we're doing 5 and 8 now.
5, open, 8, open, 5, open, 8, open, 5, open, 8, open, 5, open, 8, open.
We'll just go back and forth between those two positions.
Now if you're watching my right hand, I'm muting out the G string with my thumb and the high E string with another finger so that in case I hit it with my left hand, it doesn't ring out.
And slowly together they sound like this.
And you just repeat.
To speed it sound like this.
I hope you'll join us for our next segment which is our last segment in this video set.
I'll see you there.